Guide to the Gregory Breit Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, Circa 1929-1980; Series III; 32.5' (33 boxes)
  - Data files
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 54)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 55)
    - Subject data files, Circa 1934-1974 (Box 56)
  - Teaching files, Circa 1936-1967 (Box 57)
  - Yale University files, Circa 1950-1968 (Box 58)
  - SUNY-Buffalo files, Circa 1969-1973 (Box 59)
  - Research project files, Circa 1955-1974 (Box 60)
  - Conference files, Circa 1939-1972 (Box 61)
  - Notes, C. 1930-1980 (Box 62)
  - Personal files, Circa 1924-1973 (Box 62)
  - Restricted material
    Materials in boxes 63-65 are restricted for seventy-five years after the date appearing on the document and will be available for research between 2011 and 2050 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
    - Correspondence, Circa 1935-1973 (Box 63)
    - Yale files, Circa 1935-1973 (Box 63)
    - SUNY-Buffalo files, Circa 1935-1973 (Box 63)
    - Student files, Circa 1939-1968 (Box 64)
    - Research project files, 1946-1957, 1973-1974 (Box 65)
- Additional Material, 1917-1991; Accession 2012-M-036
  - Personal files
    - Bradbury N.E. (home file), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Condolence letters for Breit, Gregory and Keefer, Lubov Breit, 1981-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - Copies of wills - TIAA-CREF, 1919, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Gregory's father's naval device, 1917-1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Watson, W.W. home file, 1924, 1951, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Professional files
    - Correspondence - General, 1941-1949 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (A.A.A.S.), 1941-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Carnegie Institute, 1924-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)